kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
Incomprehensible
The Targeted Merchants
Did they really come this way?
But why come this way?
They shouldn't come this way
if it's as you say, Choji.
I said that because I didn't think
we were being targeted.
I don't think this is
the time to argue...
We have to formulate
some sort of strategy.
You say that, but...
What is it?
Have the guys
you spoke of caught up?
Then we should divide up
this group in two.
Here it's hard enough
to protect one.
What's the point of dividing
the group in two?
Naruto!
Please, tell us what your idea is.
This is what I mean.
For example...
Let's say there are
ten persimmons here.
Is anything okay if it's a food?
Yeah.
Then I want it to be ramen!
Naruto, it's an example, so...
Then we'll make it ramen.
Someone is after
these ten bowls of ramen.
And there are three people
to protect the ramen.
And so one person has
to protect roughly three bowls.
No, no. If it's ramen,
we should just eat it all
before they come.
That would settle things.
Naruto. This ramen is
for delivery to someone,
so we can't eat it.
Really? But the ramen
won't be tasty if it gets soggy.
I'm moving on.
If three people protect
ten bowls of ramen,
one person protects
about three bowls.
But this ramen has
legs for escaping.
Ramen with legs for escaping?!
Five bowls of ramen
quick to escape...
and five bowls of ramen
slow to escape.
Right, right..
Things are kind of getting crazy.
I see. If we divide them
into two groups...
Of course, the pursuers would target
the group that is slow to escape first.
So we have one person
defend the preceding group
and two people
for the group that is slow to escape.
Right, right.
By doing this, as for protecting
the slow group,
now one person can just protect
two and a half bowls.
Oh!
In other words, the ramen that are
quick to escape are the young people
and the ramen that are slow to escape are
the elderly people and children, right?
Exactly.
Not only will the possibility of
the former to completely
get away increase,
the burden on the latter
to protect will decrease.
It's a strategy that kills two birds
with one stone.
You're smart.
However...
the elderly people and children will...
I just stated a rational idea.
There's the possibility
of complete annihilation
if we stay in a group.
Am I wrong, Yurinoshin?
Well...
Then it's settled.
Let's divide everyone up in two.
I'm sorry, gramps.
Don't worry about it.
It would be trouble if something bad
were to happen to the men in their prime.
You've got a wife and kid
at home, right?
Then we'll be going on
ahead first, Naruto, Choji.
Right.
We're counting on you, Hinata.
Naruto and I will deal
with the pursuers.
Right. I'll protect them well.
Lady Haruna.
Yurinoshin, keep your mouth shut.
What's your mission?
Is it not to protect me?
Things will be settled if Kikusuke
defeats those guys.
Then shall we get going, too?
I'm counting on you, Brother Choji.
Right! Leave it to me!
Choji.
You go on ahead.
What?
I'm going back to check things out
at the place where the traps are.
But if you do that, you may encounter
the pursuers along the way...
That's fine.
Doing something like waiting
to be attacked isn't my style!
Naruto!
Leave it to me!
I meant...
There's no point to our strategy
if I have to protect five people
by myself.
Right, there's no point.
We came down that path,
so the trap should be
up ahead somewhere.
I guess I'll take a shortcut!
What's this? What happened?
Why is it so wet?
What are these wounds?!
This guy's...!
Are you serious?
Is something wrong, Brother Choji?
No, nothing.
I see...
I feel it.
Even I can sense this much bloodlust.
It's close now.
Rain?
This is the worst. Rain wipes out
all presence of the enemy.
This rain is weird.
Gather around, everyone!
Stay close to me.
What's this?
This is bad!
What was that now?!
Everyone! Get under the cart!
We're already under here!
You're quick!
Choji!
Naruto!
Get down!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Naruto! Could you say so
at the start
if you're going to
use paper bombs?
All right. It seems they're gone.
Why did they disappear?
Isn't it obvious?
They have no business with a shop
that doesn't have the thing they want.
Thing they want?
That's right.
If a shop's sold out
of the item you want,
you'd go to another shop, right?
Could it be that the thing that he wants
is in the other group?
What does that mean?!
Hinata's in danger!
Everyone, leave your stuff here
and take only what you need!
Hinata is?!
Everyone, we'll put up our tents here
for today and rest.
It's dangerous to move in the dark.
Hey!
We finally caught up.
Naruto, Choji. What is it?
"What is it," nothing.
The situation has changed.
It seems someone among
these people
is hiding something important.
Something important?
It should probably have something
to do with us being chased.
But who is hiding what?
It's most likely you guys,
Shun and Yurinoshin.
Don't be silly!
What are you saying we're hiding?
Don't play innocent!
Kikusuke has been killed
by someone!
What?!
Kikusuke was?!
Don't play innocent!
Kikusuke has been killed
by someone!
What?!
Kikusuke was?!
Why should he have to
suit up like a Shinobi,
fight those guys and then get killed?!
It's not necessary to tell you guys.
But if that's why we're being chased...
It means you guys are putting
everyone in danger.
If you don't tell us honestly,
we won't be able to protect
even what we can protect.
Kikunojou...
Kikunojou?
You mean Kikusuke?
Yes... And my name isn't Yurinoshin.
It's Yurinojou.
Stop, Yurinojou!
The person here is Lady Haruna,
the only daughter of the feudal lord
of the Land of Greens.
Princess?!
Princess Haruna of the Land of Greens.
You've grown up so much...
Princess...?
You were a woman?!
Lady Haruna,
it is as these people say.
We must not put everyone in danger
by hiding the truth any further.
But why is someone like a princess
mingling among merchants?
There was information of
a coup d'etat in the Land of Greens.
A coup d'etat?
The Land of Greens was a small,
but calm and peaceful land.
However, it was by no means
a prosperous land.
Before we realized it,
more than half of the public officials
had been bought off.
Who in the world would do that...?
The ringleaders are three brothers
called the Janin,
evil ninja who came from
across the sea.
Janin?
Yes. They're guys who use
a particular type of ninjutsu
and are called as such
because of their frightfulness.
They've taken many lives
and think nothing of it
if it's for their own gains.
They treat people like worms...
But why the Land of Greens?
I don't know why.
But his lordship had Lady Haruna
hide amongst a group of merchants
and got her out of the land.
Kikunojou and I were left
with the protection of the princess,
but we were insecure with
just the two of us.
So then we hurriedly commissioned
the Hidden Leaf
under the pretext of protection
from bandits.
Why didn't you tell us
something that important?
There's no way I could have.
My escape is top secret.
Besides, what would happen
if I were to have told you?
The end result would've been
you guys running away in confusion.
No way would I do something
like run away.
Kikunojou might not have
had to die if
we had understood the situation
from the start.
I wonder.
One of you guys might've ended up
like Kikunojou.
We're actually fine.
But to think you'd go so far as to involve
the old lady and the children.
It couldn't be!
Were you intending to use
the old lady and the kids as decoys
and escape just yourself?!
That's right. What of it?
Choji! Hinata!
As for me,
I'm really ticked off right now!
So what of it?!
If something should happen
in the land,
I would become
the only blood relative
of the feudal lord of
the Land of Greens.
If I can just survive,
things could be restored someday,
even if the Land of Greens
were to be destroyed.
Say what?! Just what is it
you think of people's lives?!
Please forgive her.
Yurinojou.
Is it not your mission to protect me?
You're still talking about such things...?
Please wait, Naruto!
Lady Haruna, that's true for me.
However, these people are different.
The mission they undertook
was to protect merchants.
It was not to protect us.
Indeed, what we heard about
was a D-rank mission to protect
all of the merchants.
Protecting a prominent figure of
a land is an A-rank mission.
The rank differs by far too much.
Are you guys saying
you're going to forsake me?
Weren't you saying until just now
that you didn't trust people like us?
I'll protect you with my life,
Lady Haruna...
Shut up, Yurinojou!
Kikunojou was your senior disciple.
There's no way you alone
could defeat an opponent
whom he couldn't defeat!
That will just be our destiny
when that happens, Lady Haruna.
Watch, Brother Choji.
Oh! Awesome, awesome.
I'm sorry about earlier.
It happened so suddenly,
I couldn't stop.
Don't be concerned about me.
However, please forgive Lady Haruna.
The Land of Greens is a small land.
For the sake of the land's survival,
Lady Haruna was kept under
the custody of another land,
as a hostage all by herself
since she was little.
Hostage?
It frequently happens in
a small land in a war-torn world.
When Lady Haruna returned
from the other land,
she had completely lost her feelings
of trust towards people.
Lady Haruna is also
a victim of a turbulent world.
There's a village
about one league down
the mountain from here.
For the time being,
we'll leave the old woman
and the others there.
Be careful now.
You guys, too!
Bye!
Why are you separating them from us?
They still have value for
my personal use.
Are you still going on about that?
They went so far as to discard
their merchandise for your sake.
Then we should also leave this place.
We must not.
If we go into hiding,
there's a possibility of
that group being attacked again.
Exactly. This time,
it's our turn to be the decoy
in order to protect them.
Do as you like!
Hinata, I'll take care of things here.
Please rest a while.
Yeah, do that.
Then, if you insist.
Oh, yeah. Here.
Kikunojou was holding this.
Thanks, Naruto.
Kikunojou was a master
of the Flower Ninjutsu
passed down in the Land of Greens.
We learned together
when we were little
and I couldn't beat him even once...
Now I have forever lost
the chance to beat him.
No... You still have a chance.
What?
If you beat the guy
who defeated Kikunojou,
you will have beaten Kikunojou!
Naruto... You're exactly right...!
Here they come!
Other than the fact that
the enemy uses water,
we have absolutely no idea
what they'll come at us with.
I know.
Go! Flower Ninja Art:!
Flying Flowers: Falling Foliage.
What?!
He changed the trajectory in mid-air?!
Oh, no!
I finally got you!
Gotcha.
To think you'd
make me look like a fool.
So you finally show yourself.
I will avenge Kikunojou!
Try it if you can.
I won't let you get away!
Too bad. You're one person short.
I've set a share for one more.
I don't know about that.
First, I'll take care of you, boy.
Water Style: Liquid Memory!
Naruto...!
And this!
Summoning Jutsu!
What is it?
Is that...?
The jutsu that killed Kikunojou?!
Vanish and die!
kinou wa Call Sign zenbu keitai de
yesterday's call sign was broadcast all from my phone
norenai Fuzz Guitar henna kouen de
in a strange park I play the fuzz guitar without enthusiasm
Yellow Moon
yellow moon
ima mo mittsu kazoete me wo akete
even now, counting to three I open my eyes
Shadow Moon mada yume wo miteru
shadow moon, I am still dreaming
me wo mite me wo mite se wo mukeai nagara
look at my eyes, look at my eyes, as we face one another's back
me wo mite itsu aeru
look at my eyes, when can we meet?
Every Day Every Night omoi tsuku kotoba de
every day, every night, with every word I can think of
chirakatta mama no kimochi wo ima sugu
right away, my messy feelings as is
mahou no Chord Change nemurenai machi
a magical chord change in a restless city
higawari na Jazz Guitar sotto mainaa de
a daily jazz guitar played in a soft minor key
What is this huge thing?
I don't wanna become its food.
Let me tell you one thing.
I'm not tasty.
I'm not tasty, either.
But Choji would be more
worthwhlle to eat.
No, Naruto would be tastier.
Be eaten for the sake of your comrade.
You're the one who will
become it food.
This isn't the time to be arguing
about stuff like that.
Yurinojou!
Anyway, we just have to run
with all our might for now!
Next time:
"Groundwater, The Inexhaustible Ningu."